<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Physics Tool</string>
    <string name="enter_values">Please Enter Valid Values!</string>
    <string name="choose_equation">Please Choose An Equation!</string>
    <string name="rad">Rad</string>
    <string name="deg">Deg</string>
    <string name="projexp">Projectile motion problems allow us to solve how far projected objects
    will fly. By knowing the initial velocity of an object and the angle at which it is
    projected, we can solve how long it will be in the air, and thus, how far it will fly.
    An important thing to note is that gravity is not affected by a horizontal velocity, in
    other words, if a bullet is dropped from beside a gun the instant the gun fires, the two
    bullets would hit the ground at the exact same time, this is the key to solving
    projectile motion problems.</string>
    <string name="projexp1">So, to solve a projectile motion problem, you must first split the
        initial velocity into horizontal and vertical components by multiplying the initial velocity
        by cos and sin of the angle of projection (cos for horizontal, sin for vertical).
        You then take the vertical component of the velocity, and plug it into the equation as
        shown below (let us assume an initial velocity of 2 m/s at an angle of 30° above the
        horizontal, and let us assume that the object landed at the same height as its origin
        therefore d=0…</string>
    <string name="projexp2">So, since time is constant we just substitute time and horizontal
        velocity into our displacement equation to find horizontal displacement…</string>
    <string name="help">This physics tool is designed to aid you with making quick and accurate
        calculations while you do practice problems. The equations button in the main menu will take
        you to your workspace where you can choose an equation or make quick calculations in the
        calculator, every time you calculate an answer, the value is stored in the ANS key. \nIf you
        tap on the learn button, you will be taken to the learning menu where you can choose which
        unit you would like to learn about, there are lessons and simulations available for
        educational purposes.\nFor quick conversions, check out the conversions page.</string>
</resources>
